Strike Clippings 5253
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Strike Clippings
1934-1946
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Albany Clipping Bureau
5253
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Clippings (information artifacts).
This collection consists of clippings about strikes in New York State from national and local papers made by the Albany Clipping Bureau for the School in 1946.
5557157
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 22, 2017
Scope and Contents
Clippings about strikes in New York State from national and local newspapers. This collection consists of clippings about strikes in New York State from national and local newspapers made by the Albany Clipping Bureau for the school in 1946.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State); Strikes and lockouts -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- New York (State); Collective labor agreements -- United States; Albany Clipping Bureau (Albany, N.Y.); New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
5557157
- 1934-1941; May, 1946 (Box 1)
  - 1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - May 10, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - May 13-14, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - May 16-17, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - May 18, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - May 19, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - May 20, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - May 21, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - May 22, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - May 23, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - May 24, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - May 25, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - May 26, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - May 27, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - May 28, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - May 29, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - May 30, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - May 31, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- June-November, 1946 (Box 2)
  - June 1-2, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - June 3-4, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - June 6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - June 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - June 8, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - June 9-10, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - June 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - June 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - June 13, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - June 14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - June 15-16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - June 17, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - June 18, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - June 19, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - June 20, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - June 21, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - June 22, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - June 23, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - June 24, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - June 25, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - June 26, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - June 27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - June 28, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - June 29-30, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - July 2, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - July 3, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - July 5, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - July 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - July 9-10, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - July 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - July 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - July 13, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - July 14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - July 15, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - July 16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - July 17, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - July 18, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - July 19, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - July 21, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - July 22-23, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - July 25-27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - July 28, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - July 29, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - July 30, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - August 1-3, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - August 4-6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - August 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - August 8, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - August 9, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - August 10, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - August 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - August 12-14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - August 15, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - August 16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - August 17, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - August 18, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - August 19, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - August 20, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - August 21, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - August 22, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - August 23, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - August 24, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - August 26, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - August 27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - August 28, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - August 29, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - August 30, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - August 31, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - September 1, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - September 2, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - September 3-5, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - September 6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - September 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - September 8, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - September 9, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - September 10, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - September 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - September 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - September 13, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - September 14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - September 15, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - September 16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - September 17-18, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - September 19, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - September 20, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - September 21, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - September 22, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - September 23-25, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - September 26, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - September 27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - September 28, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - September 29, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - September 30, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - October 1-2, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - October 3, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - October 4, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - October 5, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - October 6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - October 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - October 8, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - October 9, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - October 10, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - October 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - October 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - October 13, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - October 14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - October 15, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - October 16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - October 17, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - October 18, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - October 19, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - October 20, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - October 21, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - October 22, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - October 23, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - October 24, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - October 25, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - October 26, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - October 27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - October 28, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - October 29, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - October 30, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - October 31, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - November 1, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - November 2, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - November 3, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - November 4, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - November 5, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - November 6, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - November 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - November 8, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - November 9, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - November 10, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - November 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - November 12, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - November 13, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - November 14, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - November 15, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - November 16, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - November 17, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - November 18, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - November 19, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - November 21, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - November 22-27, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 144)